[Music]  his hands were once used for battle  now they've got humble tools for peace  i need to figure out  [Music]  exactly who i am  [Music]  i want to choose my own path  live in the moment  [Music]  my superheroing days are over  [Music]  remember what i told you  [Music]  you ever feel lost  just look into the eyes of the people  that you love  [Music]  not me  what just listening  [Music]  hi  there's a gun  this is the quiet car  use your small inside voice in here son  there's a gun  [Music]  [Music]  talk to me i am ready you are getting  the new and improved me  because if you put peace out in the  world do you get peace back  i think you might be forgetting what you  do for a living take the gun every job i  do somebody dies i'm not that guy  anymore  some conflicts require a gun  [Music]  hey this is nice  okay what am i snatching and or grabbing  a briefcase you said you wanted simple  for your first job back doesn't get  simpler  dude i don't even know you  there's nothing simple about this job  something else going on here  yeah i'm not the only one on this train  looking for this case  hmm where's the briefcase oh [ __ ]  [Music]  it was just here  we are right on settle everything that's  ever happened to you this is gonna sting  this  that's a [ __ ] deal  [Music]  [Applause]  oh no thank you you know what do you  have uh anything sparkling  that's the one thank you domo arigato  i'm sure you want to talk this out no  particular okay  [Music]  exclusively in movie theaters  what do we have here yeah here i thought  we were special fellas this here's  bagman hang man whatever what the hell  kind of mission is this  [Music]  everyone here is the best there is who  the hell are they gonna get to teach us  captain pete maverick mitchell  let me be perfectly blunt  you are not my first choice you were  here at the request of admiral kazansky  aka iceman he seems to think that you  have something left to offer the navy  what that is i can't imagine  you all due respect sir i'm not a  teacher  i just want to manage expectations  good morning aviators  this is your captain speaking  then we're off  here we go  in three  two  one  we're going into combat on a level no  living pilot's ever seen  not even him  you think up there you're dead believe  me  my dad believed in you  i'm not gonna make the same mistake  [Music]  someone's not coming back from this  [Music]  you will never forgive yourself  no turning back now come on  [Music]  [Music]  i wanted to show them something that  wasn't an illusion  something that was real  something that we  see and touch  creation  is an act of sheer will  life  will find a way  we can't keep her here forever  they find her we're never gonna see her  again we gotta protect her that's our  job  humans and dinosaurs can't coexist  [Music]  we created an ecological disaster  ellie settler  alan grant  you didn't come out all this way just to  catch up now did you you coming or what  [Music]  we're racing toward the extinction of  our species  we not only lack dominion over nature  [Music]  we're subordinate to it  [Music]  come back i always come back  that's another plane right  not exactly  don't move  bigger why do they always have to go  bigger  [Music]  these rings signify the commitment  so help me thomas sorry sorry  life or death situation i need you to  use the ring to save me like right now  oh lord there are two of them now  what's happening okay quick version  robotnik  i discovered the source of ultimate  power  we need to get it back for the world is  doomed  you got some kind of  space porcupine  i am an echidna warrior  hmm  hedgehog  it's time to say goodbye to humanity  welcome  to the new norm  this is your moment to be the big hero  bad time to say this but i don't  actually have a plan  hey you got a little something on your  uh  someone call an uber  it's cold in here  let's turn up the heat  i'll break the winter soldier  fear not citizen you are terrible at  this your negative attitude is not  helping  we stick together  no matter what  you're unskilled  untrained  unworthy  you forgot one  unstoppable  [Music]  knuckles you are really bad at punching  [Music]  every night  i dreamed the same dream  the nightmare begins  i did what i had to do  to protect our world  you can't control everything strange  [Music]  you open the doorway between universes  and we don't know who or what will walk  through it  wanda  what do you know about the multiverse  this had his theories  he believed it was dangerous  he was right  i'm sorry stephen  [Music]  your desecration of reality  will not go unpunished  [Music]  we should tell him the truth  [Music]  things just got out of hand  [Music]  you break the rules  become a hero  i do it i become the enemy  [Music]  that doesn't seem fair  [Music]  fate  has no mercy  um  [Music]  [Music]  [Applause]  [Music]  [Applause]  i cannot escape my faint  there are places out there you can't  find on any map  they're not gone  they're just lost  hey kid a little young for a bartender  aren't you a little old for prom aren't  you  everything in here why the map this path  ferdinand magellan took the sail around  the world you know your history  it's the biggest treasure that's never  been found 5 billion easy  to go i think you're here because you're  your brother well you know my brother  said  tally doesn't have any friends i should  know him one of them  [Music]  you are a collector well i dabbled i  don't know  my family has been looking for this  portion for a very long time so much  blood  i'm pretty sure he's just threatening to  kill me don't touch your ear like that  you look like an idiot  you have no idea who you partnered with  i've been dreaming about this stuff  since i was a kid my brother sayon left  one final clue  [Music]  family  oh my god i should never come out to  play with that big boy's man because  you're about to get a proper scottish  welcome  what crap  exclusively in movie theaters  bruce wayne  sorry i wouldn't be bothering you here  but your people keep telling me you're  unavailable  you know you really could be doing more  for this city  the family has a history of philanthropy  but as far as i can tell you're not  doing anything  the riddler  is asking for you the killer left this  for the batman why is he writing to you  you came  i've been trying to reach you  look there's latest it's all about the  wings  if we don't stand up no one will  you got a lot of cats i have a thing  about strength  i'm not so sure  i'm just here to unmask the truth about  this cesspool we call a city  you're part of this too  how am i part of this  oh you're really not as smart as i  thought you were  bruce  away  all these years  we all have our scars bruce you're still  away  he's involved in this oh he's not  involved how do you know he's up for  delany  where are you under there  what are you hiding selena they'll throw  your life away  don't worry honey i got nine of them  it can be cruel poetic or blind  but when it's denied  it's your violence you may find  justice  the answer's justice  come on vengeance  let's get into some trouble  [Music]  every night i dream about that strange  city like his calling  the target is a writer his book is  titled godslayer and the writer's name  is conglen my boss is convinced that  what happens in the story is somehow  affecting his health you only have three  days you don't want to let us down  well you're the one writing it so you  can decide what happens next  i come to kill you  show yourself  you're going up against powers beyond  your comprehension you don't even stand  a chance  the story's not done  i have to finish it  this is kimura i'm here to offer you  federal protection i know you're afraid  but you can save me right  i can help you stay alive  congratulations  you've just been erased  we've got the fbi with me we'll take  khmer in ourselves i can't let you do  that  there's been a breach you know the drill  i know what must be done  let's go grab her  game time  the mason pollard i know would never do  this something very serious must have  happened  bring him in alive  come on we gotta go green up  follower blocked mini camino's face her  biometrics and his own from the cctv  network  oh yeah was that tracking him now and  i've issued a warrant for his arrest  she needs your help i need your help  we're here for you  oh  you want me  come get me  i got you  officers down in front of the bank  automatic weapons being fired  [Music]  bank robbery suspects have taken an  ambulance  i got a cop shot gotta get him to the  hospital we're doing hostages now  i came to you for a loan you're my  brother have i ever gotten you anything  i couldn't get you out of lock  everything down  we're just trying to get home  we don't get to walk off into the sunset  i have a plan  [Music]  are following these two suspects  just chill out  gotta chill out hit me up  what's going on in there  these guys are nut jobs right here it  [Music]  [Music]  hey is up big guy just waking up  does your wife know you're up eggs  i'm sorry brother  sorry that brought you into this  take me away  i just wanted things to be the way they  used to be we are trying to save you  [Music]  i'm gonna get you back home little  brother  [Music]  and get everybody home  only in theaters april 8.  why do you want to be a samurai  [Music]  i lived in a bad part of town full of  bad dogs  everybody always picked on me  i thought if i could be a samurai  it would change everything  sounds like you need a mentor perhaps a  once great samurai who has fallen on  hard times and maybe could use some help  himself  but where can i find  one out of here who even made that it's  you don't believe everything you read  [Music]  sorry hank you have to do something  you're under arrest  you wanted to be a samurai fun isn't it  go get them  get back out there  [Music]  hey this is the training montage isn't  it sometimes you need a friend  [Applause]  nope  don't forget to land on your  send a tweet to assemble the troops  who knew an evil army could go through  so many beams  [Laughter]  [Applause]  what the mother father cocker spaniel's  going on here  the legend of hank  time to finish this  this might take a while  you led me straight to the lost city now  prepare to die there were just hundreds  of snakes in this temple just waiting  for us to show up what why aren't they  biting that guy this is ridiculous  delete delete delete  listen loretta we need you to promote  your new book on the lost city you can't  spend your life in the bathtub during  chardonnay with eyes  ladies and gentlemen the world's sexiest  cover model dash mcmahon  you do know you're not dash right dash  is a character i made up  oh my god  oh crap  miss sage i enjoyed your book about the  lost city and i believe you're the one  who can help me find its treasure  i have to respectfully decline i'm  afraid i must insist  unchain me that's your seatbelt  loretta sage is missing i'm going to  rescue her i just want her to think of  me as more than a cover mom outstanding  dangerously  alan what are you doing here we're here  to save you i'm certified cpr i'm served  by crossfit  i have snacks after them  this is like your book we're on the love  more and dash adventure right now i'm  gonna help you out a little bit let's go  what are you doing don't do that  get out of there this is not a romance  novel jungles eat people like us what is  that get it off give me a second i can  feel them  we're so close i could actually find the  lost city  if i don't get to this island my friend  and her cover model are going to die i  am driving oh oh oh oh  loretta sage getting you out of here why  are you so handsome my dad was a weather  man  hey oh she doesn't need saving in there  uh what are you doing in there  [Music]  [Music]  mrs wang are you with us  i am paying attention  now you may only see a pile of proceeds  but i see a story  i can see where this story is going  it does not look  good  what's happening  evelyn  i'm not your husband i'm one of the  fusion if i'm from another universe i'm  here because we need your help  very busy today so time to help you  across the multiverse  i've seen thousands of evidence  you can access  their  even the skills  there's a great evil surprise about the  many verses  and you  may be your only chance of stopping it  don't make me find you i am really good  i don't believe you  ah  the universe he speaks of senseless  things is so much bigger  remember our mission concerning the fate  of every single world of our infinite  multiverse  there is no way i am the evelyn you are  looking for  every rejection  every disappointment  has led you here  to this  moment  don't let anything distract you from it  [Music]  the old wars  cold war war on terror  he knew who we were fighting  but now the enemy is invisible  they can destabilize entire countries  from simple reach of their keyboard  [Music]  officially i can't put you on this  but if you were to go out on your own  i would need some help  i'm guessing this isn't a social pool  i'm putting together a team and you're  the best in the world of what you do  i thought this was done i'll be back for  dinner tomorrow  [Music]  hands put your gun down please five four  three two one pull the trigger or you  can listen  we all work for different intelligence  agencies  american  british  german colombian chinese  but now we have a common enemy and if we  don't stop then  let's start world war iii  so we need to join forces  this is like half the cia's most wanted  you bump i grab  i like the new team we'll take it from  here  i've got four more agents out on the  street i counted six but thanks for the  tip  i have two children  i am a normal person i cannot do this  anymore the bad guys are out there right  now you go home  you bring them with you  are you under control are you  no  we put ourselves in danger  so others aren't  [Music]  [Music]  355.  if you're watching this thing you know  by now a huge problem is heading our way  an emergency meeting is being called our  usual place immediately shrink bagels  i've made a shocking discovery  i needed to get me in touch with nasa  immediately well nasa and i aren't  really on speaking terms these days well  that'll change  when you tell them that the moon is out  of orbit  there's no need to panic knocks racing  why are they lying about all this  it's too late to stop  you knew all this was happening before  nasa  you're the unidentified source oh yes  we're dealing with an intelligent entity  we're planning a mission to attack this  thing  i'm asking you for your help  say yes brian  i needed to be brave  if the moon really is what you think it  is  suit up  horizon you have got a big gravity  weight coming your way you have to  launch now did he say gravity wave  trouble  we're underwater guys  uh  that's crazy  what's the plan save the mill and save  earth  ray what are you doing  let's find itself  wait for it  let's go you son of a [ __ ]  [Music]  [Music]  it's on airplane mode  [Music]  [Music]  she's out  [Applause]  so  [Music]  wake up buddy it is one o'clock  maybe i should let him sleep  okay  [Music]  [Music]  we'll go for a walk  i have an owner and he's superman let me  just turn that out  i should call me iron man  no  my dog's the best but he's not the  greatest with other animals what is new  with you fellow normal dog i bit the  fedex guy the other day who was he  working for general zod the legion of  doom  [Music]  fedex of course the federation of x's  not to be trusted  what is taking my owner so long  well well well  if it isn't the justice league  superman  what's going on  you're super strong i should be a lot  more dead right now right  my best friend is in danger and you have  to help me well we're just a bunch of  shelter pets  but they're stronger than you think the  mighty oil  i didn't see anything show on wheels  where the heck am i indestruct dog  when one has an abundance of power  they have a certain duty to use that  power to  [Music]  sorry you were saying something  how much did you have to drink i had two  toilet bowls and a bidet but day too  just which is crazy i didn't even know  that was a thing but it's like a dog  water fountain  oh out of the way cat child  hey deploy canine idea what  excellent shielding that seemed  incredibly painful  anybody want to switch powers  as a private contractor  you're possessing a unique set of skills  [Music]  what's that  power nap you said it was clear i said  the front was clear  front back right wrong  anyway shall we  so what we got something rather nasty  has been stoned  we have to stop that getting onto the  open market  who's the buyer greg simmons the  billionaire armstealer  oh a lot very serious faces up here in  there you can't catch this fish with  conventional lures i'm sorry the lure  being daddy francesco  the movie star greg simmons favorite  movie star and how do we get him  blackmail  who's to gear  very good carry on  the world needs you for your greatest  role yet who are you i'm your new  manager  there's a sensitive and awkward  situation between you and your  sister-in-law i actually love my  sister-in-law  it's  [Music]  okay i'm ready  let's go to work will someone pinch me  please is that danny francesco what's  next for you i'm playing a mysterious  self-made billionaire  you just described me  shadow maybe do whatever i do  whatever i do  whoever greg was buying from was amongst  you last night the ukrainians  i can get inside the ukrainians  i hope you take them to dinner first  before you get inside of them  sexually  they're gonna kill you now we'll shoot  first then my eyes will see  what tidy you recognize your awesome  fortune that is a sexy name cover's  blown we're burnt what do i do the mood  you start is going to melt  you stop daddy francesca  what are you gonna do with that  so you weren't seen by anyone  yes  that's yes do you want seen by anyone  yes or yes you were seen by someone  yes  [Music]  one day you wake up and realize you're  not sure who the good guys are anymore  you're a federal agent involved in a  secret fbi program off the books what  kind of bad stuff do you do breaking and  entering  physical coercion  you name it i've probably done it  murder  not on my menu  grandpa  gabe i've been thinking maybe it's time  i hang it up no  travis not an option  i know i wasn't a great father but i'd  like to be the best grandfather i can be  natalie doesn't need a fixer like you  i've been writing about the story for  over a year  the united states government is killing  innocent civilians under the guise of  protecting democracy  under whose orders the director of the  fbi  how many would have to die for you to  stop looking the other way  [Music]  you need to complain  you're confused about our relationship  you are my weapon you work for me  count me out you show me a little  gratitude if you want a normal life  my hand is now  [Music]  where's my family  if i find out you had anything to do  with my granddaughter disappearing  you're gonna need more men  you'll be finished before the day is  over  everything i did  is for you  are you really gonna shoot me travis  yes i will  grandpa are you a good guy  i wanna be  [Music]  was looking in your file  you're not the usual fish are you  i see that sort of behavior  as an advantage for you  it could be advantageous to everyone  including your country  want a gig  tell me more  we kidnap people  and transport them to other countries  willing to look the other way while we  interrogate them  what do you want do you know this guy  he's radicalizing young kids you got a  20 on the target  you know what's required get your hands  dirty  no restraints target's secure  the clock is ticking  somebody is really aching for this guy  there's something they're not telling us  i'm just a foot soldier they don't tell  me  more we know the more we're accountable  to  our mission is to keep the wars small  and sacrifice is meaningful  just because you're american  doesn't mean your colleagues share the  same goal as you  we have a problem  why are we descending  there's been a major shift i pulled the  plug that guy knew we were coming it's  definitely a trap  for all we know this guy's controlling  the whole goddamn thing  we're next we get ready  all i know is control in order  for some bigger picture we're not seeing  no matter how messy this gets  i'm not your enemy  we play a complicated game allegiances  change  we're officially in cleanup mode  time for plan b  so what's plan b  kill em all  extraction 10 seconds  let's do it  [Music]  oh  michael  what have you done i was trying to help  people  but the cure  it's a curse  i have powers that can only be described  as superhumans  but there's a cost  now a face of choice to hunt  and consume blood  don't die  we all have monsters within us  it's up to us to control it  what if i can't  michael morbius  you've been given a gift  not  exactly time to let go of what you used  to be  discover who you're meant to be  all our lives we've lived with death why  shouldn't they know what it feels like  for a change  just accept who you are  the bad guy  more bs  holy water really  yeah you ever see lost boys story of my  life  a new marvel legend arrives exclusively  in movie theaters april 1st  i noticed the moment you walked in the  door  you have that extra something special  you're a real star  [Music]  i'm tired of playing to mid-sized crowds  in nashville we can do something bigger  [Music]  cheers still early y'all gonna raise  some hell or what let me grab my purse  oh my god or for dutch lee and i are  obsessed with the duchess sisters  is that her house yeah  what if i told you i got harper dutch's  address how did you get that caleb gave  it to me  oh i bet he did  [Music]  we can't just show up at our house  [Music]  so you want me to do a song with you  [Music]  y'all any good well we'd love to show  you which one of you is better oh we're  equals yeah you better drink my damn  booze  torn hearts with harper dutch is a great  idea we're doing a saltwater  this is how we celebrate  [Music]  this is weird pretty sure harper killed  hope  oh my god  harper's trying to turn us against each  other  this is my house i will tear it to  shreds to get to you too  the girls just came by for some free  advice on a whim nothing's free in  nashville is it  [Music]  kingsman world's finest tailor but now  we're going into the spy business  very clever based on true events  this will not be a war of heroes  [Music]  meet history's most evil legends  the assassin gavrilo princip weakness  throwing arm  strength  started world war one  the super spy  mata hari strength  screen presence  weakness  scarves do you forget your manners  guilty as charged  have a crazed monkey  respiratory  strength  and weaknesses  you'll have to see it for yourself  is good now yes  on december 22nd our enemies think we  are gentlemen  it's time to remind them  what the kingsmen are  nobility is born  in blood  [Music]  boys are always so messy  the king's man only in theaters december  22nd  what's a better soldier you're my dad  careful  come on let's go did you actually see my  dad's wife  yes  we looked after each other  brothers  yeah kind of like brothers  james the cleaning house  you're leaving the army with an  honorable discharge but you're losing  your pension and health care  we gave them our minds our bodies and  our spirit  and they'd shoot us up and spit us out  i just want to check in with y'all on  your past due payment message deleted  what you did in uniform sledgehammer  [ __ ]  our thing scalpel work  we operate a deep black og offshoot with  direct presidential authority  bank some decent cash put a down payment  on the house  it's not dangerous now i know you're  lying maybe i need to take care of my  family so what do you say you're down  for the cause yeah  salim mohammed mosu study pathogenic  influenza viruses in humans  we all know what one motivated radical  can do  so let's cowboy up get it done and get  home to our families you don't  understand what you're doing i'm trying  to save lives  this is only about money  what did we do mike  i've got an extraction team brown bmw x1  comply i'll do that when you confirm who  you're working for you work for me you  gotta trust me i am trying to help you  oh we're working for the president or  corporation  they train us to run their errands  kill their enemies and kill each other  it's easy to kill but it's much harder  to survive  need to get back home  home's a memory  [Music]  he's going to come after you with  everything he's got  [Music]  i'm going home  [Music]  henry  celia it's been a long time  they've opened the books on flight 127.  the hijackers had help from inside our  station here in vienna  we need to find out if we had a mold  [Music]  vic has me looking into flight 127. so  this is an interview  i thought you were here to see if we  still had that old spark  it's old friends  oh you can do better than that  told lovers  december 2012 paint me and celia's  picture i was living the dream then  flight 127 happened  the hijacking appears to have taken the  most tragic  someone in our station betrayed us what  about you they cleared me  really  if we started shouting mole that would  have been it for all of us we look at  the evidence we follow the facts are you  accusing me  we want to keep this quiet we can't  afford the embarrassment of a  prosecution if it's celia harrison i  need to know the man i send can do  what's necessary  [Music]  got her right here in front of me i can  do this clean but it has to happen now  it's the things that we don't know that  get to me  [Music]  what we had was real  wasn't it  do you know anything about wine a little  you're a lightsaber i'm chris  skye  two sudden adventures it's a sudden  adventure  [Music]  hey get away from my car man we don't  want any problems  wait wait wait  ladies you're two weeks behind on the  rent again you're not gonna say anything  explain where you were all night  i saw something on the news lisa it's  your roommate  scott i should probably contact the  police that would be stupid of me why  expecting a package  how's the knee dude i do good work don't  i  everything goes loverboy  stripping down to the studs  that's scary right i need all your  passwords and security codes  are you going to get chris so you want  me to call the police he's right here  daddy what do you want  my name is christopher decker there's a  woman in my house she's imprisoned me  against my will she's trying to steal my  identity she wants to kill me  thank god you came back chris thought i  might lose you forever i'm better now  you should have seen a look on your face  [Music]  [Music]  stay back  afraid of the dark  i love the dark  [Music]  the germans must be coming he can smell  them  who the red coast  they say he sent 100 crowds to meet  their maker  who has seen the red ghost  maybe he's immortal  eins get ready for battle  try  grenade  [Music]  it's our chance maybe your only hope  this is my home  just tell us your name  hello  come  it's been a year 16 months  you're a hard guy to get to really know  do you even want a family  i do want a family  [Music]  my name's perry i i work for grace  he wants you this address  i get  [Music]  i know who you are i know your name of  course your reputation precedes you  work for me i'm done with that really  hard  you're gonna be fun to have a route  440 grand in here  we're gonna make this exchange or i'm  just gonna take it  i mean you do have some balls  can i find out excuse me boys  do you guys mind moving out of the way  maybe somewhere over there  do you wanna grab yours i'll grab mine  where are you driving off to in the  middle of a tuesday ray  you know not much  [Music]  he got away  you know what this guy really knows how  to handle himself  so that makes things a little harder  [Applause]  oh my god  let me get you out of here okay i'm sure  you will you're here to take me thank  you  i went out of here too  one shot  can you run  can you run no but i'm gonna hover like  hell  [Music]  i'm gonna get away from all this  violence  starting  now  yeah now it's good  [Music]  we all understand betrayal some of us it  was a system maybe it was our families  could have been a stranger  nothing i love more than watching grown  men smear  [Music]  we are men we founded this country on  our backs now they want us to give up  power  willingly into the hands of people who  are incapable of wielding it  over my dead body  [Music]  what are we doing kind of like a pain at  the streets program  look i don't smack you in the mouth i'd  like to see you trying  there's some feminists who want to  attack my event  i need additional protection  she's going to be in a body bag before  sundown  no one's going to give it to us so we  have to take it  the violence you know it's gonna come  back to you it always does  you guys are professional murderers  you're coming for your blood remember  boys be nice  [Music]  it's amazing so far  we are here for this nothing which is  exactly what we're gonna do the whole  time we're here  wait a room above the water is that safe  i hope i guess  oh my god  we could be anywhere what are we gonna  do  we need to focus on surviving  how long can we last in all this  they'll come for us  [Applause]  what was that what i just saw something  this is shark  [Music]  we're not gonna die  we're gonna be okay  [Music]  [Music]  [Music]  [Music]  foreign  no wrong tv  [Music]  [Music]  another  so  [Applause]  [Music]  you